TINH TRAN DAC

.NET SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Address: Huong Van, Huong Tra, Thua Thien Hue, Viet Nam

Phone: +(84)973822918

Skype: <u>thtrandactinh@gmail.com</u> **Mail**: <u>thtrandactinh@gmail.com</u>

Date of birth: 14/10/1998

Gender: Male

Professional Summary

Majoring in Software Engineer and my focus is the Microsoft technologies (ASP .NET MVC5, ASP .NET Web Api,Entity Framework and LinQ to Entity). I worked as a Web Developer for over 1.5 years, from 2018 to 2020. Solid knowledge and experience about "OOP" and "Software Design and Development". The hobbies are swimming, football and watching movies.

Skills

- Asp.NET API
- Asp API Core
- Linq to Entity
- Web Design patterns
- Coding Optimization

- ASP .NET MVC
- ASP MVC Core
- Entity Framework
- MSSQL Server
- PostgreSQL

Work History

SoftWorld Vietnam Co., Ltd. – Hue, Viet Nam

2/2019 - 8/2019

- Interned there for 2 months, then started working part-time since February 2019 to August 2019.
- Internal projects development.
- As a Back-End Developer .
- Testing and bug fixing.
- Documentation.

// PROIECT

Multiple choice Test Manager Website (02/2019 - 05/2019)

- Customer: Internship Project.
- Description: Build a website for testing applicant's knowledge by multiple choice method while being interviewed.



- Team size: 1
- My position: Intern.
- Technologies used: ASP.NET MVC, MSSQL Server, Javascript, HTML, Jquery, CSS.

Internal Human Resource Management Website (05/2019 - 08/2019)

- Customer: Internal project.
- Description: Written as both an internal tool and a personal demonstration for learning .NET web development. Used .NET MVC Boilerplate for quick development. Assistant website for the company's human resource management.
- Team size: 2
- My position: Developer.
- My responsibilities: Backend services development, API for usage in mobile application development.
- Technologies used: MSSQL Server, C#, .NET Core .

3S Intersoft – Hue, Viet Nam.

9/2019 - Now

- As a Back-End Developer.
- Build new frameworks for projects related to DotNet technologies.
- Upgrade the Web applications according by customer requirements.
- Testing and bug fixing.
- Documentation.

//PROJECT

SDT Project (09/2019 - 11/2019)

- Customer: Japanese customer.
- Description: The project is to create a web app for Employee's Insurance and retirement information.
- Team size: 7-10
- My position: Developer.
- My responsibilities: write unit tests and module test.
- Technologies used: VB.NET, MSSQL Server, C#.

EMR Project (12/2019 - 02/2020)

- Customer: USA customer.
- Description: The project is to build a software for patient's medical record management and integration with a third party software to store patient test results and prescriptions.
- Team size: 10-12
- My position: Developer.
- My responsibilities: Backend services development.
- Technologies used: ASP.NET API, MSSQL Server, C#.

ITR Project (03/2020 - 07/2020)

• Customer: Vietnamese customer.

- Description: The Project is to build an IT Resource Connect System for Thua Thien Hue province.
- Team size: 7-10
- My position: Developer.
- My responsibilities: As a main Back-End developer of the project, review code for BE members in the project and join build frameworks for projects. Beside, also participates in business analysis and db construction.
- Technologies used: ASP.NET Core API, PostgreSQL, C#.

Education

- Oct 2016 Present.
- Hue University of Science.
- Software Engineering .

Interests

- Listen to music.
- Playing video games and going on vacations.
- Sport is immortal passion.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Calm under stress.
- Hardworking.
- Can work alone and teamwork well.
- Can learn stuffs pretty well on my own.